http://www.blbglaw.com/misc/legal

LEGAL NOTICE
Our Website - No Attorney-Client Relationship or Legal Advice
This site contains general information about Bernstein Litowitz Berger & Grossmann LLP (“BLB&G”).  The materials on this web site have been prepared for information purposes only and are not intended as legal advice.
The reader should not consider information on this site to be an invitation for any attorney-client relationship, and our transmission of this information and your receipt of this information are not intended to create and do not constitute an attorney-client relationship. No user of this site should act or refrain from acting on the basis of information included on this site without seeking legal advice of counsel in the relevant jurisdiction.  BLB&G expressly disclaims all liability in respect to actions taken or not taken based on any contents of this site.  Internet subscribers and online readers should not act upon this information without seeking advice from professional counsel.  Any communication with the firm through this site is not secure or confidential, and does not create an attorney-client relationship.
Bernstein Litowitz Berger & Grossmann LLP does not maintain and is not responsible for the information, contents, accuracy, completeness, usefulness or adequacy of any resources that can be accessed with hypertext links from www.blbglaw.com.
The hiring of a lawyer is an important decision that should not be based solely upon advertisements. Before you decide, ask us to send you free written information about our qualifications and experience.
Attorney Advertising Notice
Prior results do not guarantee a similar outcome. If you have any questions concerning attorney advertising rules, please contact us at:
Bernstein Litowitz Berger & Grossmann LLP  1251 Avenue of the Americas  44th Floor  New York, NY 10020  Tel: 212-554-1400  Fax: 212-554-1444  email: blbg@blbglaw.com
Our Publications
Bernstein Litowitz Berger & Grossmann LLP's publications should not be construed as legal advice on any specific facts or circumstances. Their contents are intended for general information purposes only and may not be quoted or referred to in any other publication or proceeding without the prior written consent of the Firm, to be given or withheld at our discretion. To request reprint permission for any of our publications, please use our "Contact Us" form, which can be found on this site. The mailing of our publications is not intended to create, and receipt of them does not constitute, an attorney-client relationship. The views set forth therein are the personal views of the author and do not necessarily reflect those of the law firm or company with which he or she is associated.
***
PRIVACY POLICY
Bernstein Litowitz Berger & Grossmann is committed to protecting your privacy. This includes observing relevant legal and regulatory requirements and employing appropriate security measures in order to protect your personal information.
Our policy with respect to the information that we collect, use and disclose through this website is set forth below.  This Privacy Policy is limited only to the information that we collect through this website, and does not apply to our off-line practices or policies.
This Privacy Notice explains how we collect and use your personal information. If you have any questions, please contact us at privacy@blbglaw.com.
How we collect your personal data
We collect your data directly from you, for example when you fill out mailing list/newsletter subscription form or inquiry form; or emailing us directly; or should you contact our firm.
Sometimes where you gave your consent to the third party organizations to share your data with organizations like ours, we collect data from such third parties.
We use the personal information you provide us, including your name, email address to send occasional informational emails or to respond to an inquiry you might initiate.
We may also automatically collect other, non-personally identifiable, information each time you visit this site, including, without limitation:
Technical information, including the Internet protocol address used to connect your computer to the Internet, browser type and version and device type and version.
Usage data and information about your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL), clicks to, through and from this Site (including date and time), page response times, download errors, and length of visits to certain pages.
Information from cookies and similar technologies (see Cookie Policy below).
General location information to identify where our audience views the Site from.
Some of the information described above can be collected by us only if you enable them on your hardware or software. For example, it is your option (and under your control) to accept or delete cookies, to enable location information, and to control the information that your browser transmits.
How we use your personal data
Data protection law says that we can only use personal data if we have a proper reason to do so. For example, these reasons include fulfilling a contract we have with you, when we have a legal duty, when it is in our legitimate interest or when you consent to its use. When data protection law allows us to process your personal data for our own legitimate interests, it is only allowed provided those interests do not override your own interests and/or your fundamental rights and freedoms.
At this time, the only way we use your personal data is to communicate with you either in response to an inquiry, to alert on developments in our practice, inform you of events taking place regarding our practice that may be of interest to you, or sending you our newsletter.
We may also share information
with our data processors and partners, for example, Animus Rex (our Website partner), Constant Contact (the email transmission service for our newsletter); Google Gmail (our business email provider) Google Cloud Platform (our secure cloud hosting service), all of which are required to enable the Website’s smooth operation as well as our business functions.
with lawful third parties or authorities for the purpose of preventing fraud and spam activity or if personal information is requested as part of a lawful investigation.
We do not share your personal data with any other third party and do not sell information for advertising or promotional purposes.
Retaining your personal data
We will retain your data for as long as we are obliged, under relevant legislation and regulation, or where no such rules apply, for no longer than it is necessary for our lawful purposes, and until you notify us to delete your data.
Your individual privacy rights
You have the right to object to how we process your personal data. You also have the right to see what personal data we hold about you. You can ask us to correct inaccuracies, delete or restrict personal data or ask for some of your personal data to be provided to someone else. These rights are explained in more detail below.
Requests to exercise your rights to your personal data can be made using the inquiry form on our contact page.
If you are an EU Citizen, you have these rights:
To be informed: You have the right to be provided with clear, transparent and easily understandable information about how we use your data and your rights. We fulfill this right by giving you this notice.
Access to your personal data: You can request access to a copy of your personal data.
Right to withdraw and opt-out: You may unsubscribe from our mailing list by clicking here
Right to object: You may object to our processing of your personal data by us.
Rectification: You can ask us to change or complete any inaccurate or incomplete personal data held about you.
Erasure: This is also known as “the right to be forgotten” and this means that you can ask us to delete your personal data where it is no longer necessary for us to use it, you have withdrawn consent (where applicable), or where we have no lawful basis for keeping it or otherwise using it. There are limited exceptions, for example where we need to use the information to bring or defend a legal claim.
Portability: You can ask us to provide you or a third party with some of the personal data that we hold about you in a structured, commonly used, electronic form, so it can be easily transferred. This is limited to personal data you have provided with your consent or in relation to the products you have with us, and which we process by automated means, such as your account transaction data.
Restriction: You can ask us to restrict the personal data we use about you where: it is inaccurate; you have asked for it to be erased; you have objected to our use of it; or where you need this for the bringing or defending of legal claims. When you have asked us to restrict the use of your personal data we may still store your information but will not use it further without your consent, unless we need to process it: to bring or defend legal claims; to protect the rights and freedoms of other individuals; or for other important public interest reasons.
Please note that though not all privacy laws are as strict as the EU GDPR, we will generally extend these concepts of privacy and transparency to all users since we feel that privacy is important.
Please also note that the only private data we control and process from is the information you’ve given us, which is typically your name and email address – or a note if you’ve sent us an inquiry. We do not store or track any other personal data.
If you wish to exercise any of your rights above, please contact us with your request at privacy@blbglaw.com or by using the form on our contact page
Cookie Policy
Upshot: The cookies we use on www.blbglaw.com do not contain any information that personally identifies you and we do not manually or programmatically link cookie identifiers with the personal information stored in our system. The cookies we set are used to track if a user is logged in or not and also for anonymous web traffic analysis.
What are Cookies?
A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies can be used by web servers to identity and track users as they navigate different pages on a Website and identify users returning to a Website.
Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies. A persistent cookie consists of a text file sent by a web server to a web browser, which will be stored by the browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date (unless deleted by the user before the expiry date). A session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.
How can you control the use of cookies from this Site?
If you don't want us to use cookies when you use this Site, you can adjust your internet browser settings not to accept cookies. Your web browser's help function should tell you how to do this. Alternatively, to find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to manage and delete them, visit the Website: http://www.allaboutcookies.org.
We currently set the following cookies:
Google Analytics: We use Google Analytics – the web analytics service provided by Google Inc. The Google Analytics cookies track activity on this Site but do not collect personal information about you. Rather, usage information is stored in aggregate and we use it to see trends and patterns, so we can optimize your user experience.
You may disable scripts run by Google Analytics to the extent that your browser and associated programs provide such functionality. To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all Websites, visit this Website: http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout. Google’s privacy and compliance policies are available at: https://privacy.google.com
Session ID: This is a temporary session cookie used to track whether traffic is logged in or out of this Site. Session ID cookies do not collect personal information about you and are deleted when you close your browser.
Contact us
This Website is owned and operated by Bernstein Litowitz Berger & Grossmann LLP.  If you have any questions about our privacy policy or cookie policy, please contact us at privacy@blbglaw.com or +1-212-554-1400 or +1-800-380-8496 – ask for the Marketing Department.
